(Sheldon:)Now, I know he said it's promising
(Sheldon:)and he's going to collaborate on it,
(Sheldon:)but now that you and I are friends
again, I am at your disposal.
And, frankly, lending my name
(Sheldon:)and reputation to it will help,
because a lot of people think
(Sheldon:)that you're a washed-up has-been.
(Sheldon:)Or dead.
(Arthur:)I should be so lucky.
So, what do you say?
(Howard:)You know,
if it's all the same with you,
I think I'll stick with Leonard.
(Sheldon:)It's because I'm annoying, right?
I know it is. Say it.
(Sheldon:)Say it. Say I'm annoying.
(Arthur:)-Good night.
-Say it.
(Sheldon:)Arthur, say it.
Say I'm annoying. Say it. Say it.
(Sheldon:)I'm annoying. Say it.
You're annoying!
Wow, that really hurt.
(Leonard:)If you would have told me
when I was a kid
(Leonard:)that someday
I would be doing science
(Leonard:)next to Professor Proton,
I would not have believed you.